Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory7 Mss.B.B61.inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents J
  - Jaffers, Frances C. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p.
      See Jeffers, Frances C.
  - Jagillan, I.? (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 13; 2p.
  - Jahn, A. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p.
  - Jakel, Theo (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27; 1p.
      (Enc: The Germanistic Society of America. Officers and members.)
  - Jakobson, Roman (Box 47)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), Nov. 6, 1941
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 13; 1p.
  - Jalisco, Gobernador (Box 47)
    - From Charis?, Elena Aguilar, 1911 Dec. 16
  - James, Arthur Curtiss (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 June 13
  - James, Edmund J. (Box 47)
    - E.J. James -- to Monroe Smith, 1909 Feb. 2
  - James, Edwin L. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 30; 2p.
      (Attached: Clipping)
  - James, J.B. Jr. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, ? Apr. 30
  - James, Mrs. M. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
  - Jameson, J. Franklin (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1963 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - J.F. Jameson -- to MacMillan Company, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Jameson, R.D. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1940 June 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: Note on Library of Congress fellowships or internships), 1940 June 18; 1p.
  - Janardhana, R. (Box 47)
    - R. Janardhana -- to S.V. Ramaswamy, 1932 June 4; 1p.
    - R. Janardhana -- from M.W.W.M. Yeatts, 1932 June 2
  - Janowsky, Al. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept. 9; postcard
  - Jans, William (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1904 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
  - Japanese American Committee for Democracy (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas
    - (See Nakano, K.M.N. See Takagi, Y., Mar. 6, 1942
  - Japikse, N. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc: Niederlandischer Kommittee zur Erforschung des Ursachendes Weltkrieges. Arbeits-program.), 1924 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 9; 3p.
  - Jarres, K. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - K. Jarres -- from K. Schneider, 1933 June 7
  - Jastrow, Joseph (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 2; postcard
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 3; postcard
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 6; postcard
    - To Boas, 1893 July 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1894 July 1
    - To Boas, 1894 July
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1898 July 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 14; 1p.
  - Jastrow, Morris, Jr. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 29; p.c.
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 11; p.c.
  - Jastrow, Rachel S. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan.
  - Javits, B.A. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 24; 1p.
  - Jayne, Horace H.F. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Jeffers, Frances C. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 1p.
      (Enc: Questionnaire)
      See Jaffers, Frances C.
  - Jelenko, E.W. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 3; 2p.
    - E.W. Jelenko -- from F.S. Weinman, 1934 Feb. 2
  - Jelliffe, Smith Ely (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Jena. Universitatsbibliothek (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug.
      (See Sihler, Ernest Verzeichnis)
  - Jenkens, H.D. (Box 47)
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 14; 2p.
  - Jenks, Albert Ernest (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 June 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 12; 1p.
  - Jenks, Jeremiah W. (Box 47)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 23; 7p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 2; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 12
    - From Boas, 1908 May 13
    - From Boas, 1908 June 3
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9
    - From Boas, 1908 June 26; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1908 July 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Sept. 3; 8p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 11; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 11; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc: Statements of salaries to be paid student by Immigration Commission), 1909 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 June 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Sept. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 18; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 31; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 31; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5
    - From Boas, 1910 June 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1902 May 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 20
    - To Boas, 1908 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 June 16
    - To Boas, 1908 June 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 5; 1p.
    - See Hull, Charles May 8, 1909 telegram., 1909 May 12; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 21; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 July 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 July 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 May 13
    - To Boas, 1910 June 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 13
    - To Boas, 1910 July 30
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 29; 2p.
  - Jenness, Diamond (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Aug. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - (Enc: Topics for Pacific congress), 1931 May 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - (Enc: List of linguistic material), 1929 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - (Enc: Plan of symposium papers for book), 1930 May 8; 2p.
    - (Enc: Decisions re fifth Pacific Science Congress), 1930 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - D. Jenness -- to F.E. Lathe, 1931 Dec. 9
  - Jennings, H.S. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 13; 2p.
  - Jensen, Dana O. (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 29; 1p.
  - Jensen, H. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 12; 2p.
  - Jensen, P. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 12; 4p.
  - Jerome, V.J. (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 8; 1p.
  - Jespersen, Otto (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 1p.
  - Jessen, Karl D. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 21; 1p.
  - Jessup, W.A. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 4; 1p.
  - Jesup, Morris K. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1897 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1897 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Mar. 21; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Mar. 21; 6p.
    - See Putnam, F.W. June 15, 1898., 1898 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 May 20; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1899 May 30
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 12; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 9; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 26; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 24; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 25; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 May 2
    - From Boas, 1905 May 20
    - From Boas, 1905 May 20
    - From Boas, 1905 May 23
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1905 July 6
    - From Boas, 1905 July 20
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 20
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1904 n.d.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 May 2
    - To Boas, 1905 May 2
    - To Boas, 1905 May 5
    - See Boas, F. May 17, 1905., 1905 May 24
    - To Boas, 1905 May 24
    - To Boas, 1905 July 8
    - To Boas, 1905 July 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - To Boas "Saturday eve", 1907 Sept. 16
    - To Boas "15th", 1907 Sept.
    - M.K. Jesup -- to The Grand Duke Konstantin Konstantinovitch, 1900 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - M.K. Jesup -- to George V.L.Mayer, 1905 Dec. 6
    - M.K. Jesup -- to U.S. Secretary of State, 1904 Mar. 25; 2p.
  - Jesup North Pacific Expedition (Box 48)
    - See Hunt, George, 1900-1901
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar.; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar.; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 6
  - Jette, J. (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1914 June 28
  - Jewett, Frank B. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - (Enc: List), 1941 Nov. 10; 1p.
  - Jewish Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 25; 1p.
  - Jewish Board of Guardians (Box 48)
    - See Moss, Maude, 6-23-36, 6-30-36
  - Jewish Quarterly Review (Box 48)
    See Adler, Cyrus
  - Jewish Social Service Association (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Jewish University-Committee, Vienna (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 25
    - (Attached to letter from Boas, F. to Adler, Cyrus), dated 8-25-20
  - Jijon? G. (Box 48)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
  - Jijon y Caamano, J. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1942 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 23; 1p.
  - Jobbins, Jane E. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 10
  - Jobling, James W. (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - J.W. Jobling -- from J.B. Moore, 1920 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - (Attached to letter from Moore, J.B. to Boas, F., dated Apr. 2, 1920)
  - Jochelson, Waldemar (Box 48)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 May 24
    - From Boas, 1906 June 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 June 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept. 4
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 May 2
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - From Boas, 1907 May 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 12; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19
    - From Boas, 1908 May 22
    - From Boas, 1908 May 29
    - From Boas, 1909 Sept. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 May 6
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1921 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 May 17
    - To Boas, 1906 June 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 June 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 June 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 July 5
    - To Boas, 1906 July 17; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 July 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 11; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 15